

CONTACT



Banglore, INDIA



+91 7987339295



https://www.behance.net/ nmohinirao



nmohini73@gmail.com

EXPERTISE

WRITTEN AND VERBAL COMMUNICATION

TIME MANAGEMENT

ATTENTION TO DETAIL

DESIGN TOOLS

INTERESTS







Travel

Music

Painting

FREELANCER GRAPHIC DESIGNER

FWD App , Health Highway

Create media products such as magazines, labels, advertising and signage

N MOHINI

SALES PROFESSIONAL/ DESIGNER

Motivated sales professional with a track record of exceeding targets and building client relationships. Accomplished designer with a flair for aesthetics and user-friendly designs. Blending sales skills and design expertise for exceptional results that fuel business growth.

EDUCATION

IGNOU

2021-2024

2016-2018

BACHELOR OF ARTS (TOURISM

Diploma in Computer

STUDIES)

Applications

Dr. C.V. Raman University

2016-2018

UPU Government Polytechnic Durg

Diploma in electronics and communication engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Spenza

Freelancer designer Aug 2023 - Present

Responsible for handling Social media post and content and all other creative requirments.

The invERSITY

Inside Sales Associate Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

Responsible for handling calls and identifying sales opportunities B2B2C.

Fleek

Catalog Associate May **2021 -** Nov **2022**

Ensuring that product information is accurate, accessible, and appealing to customers, ultimately contributing to a positive shopping experience.

Vedantu

Academic counselor Aug 2020 - Dec 2020

Advise students/ parents for their learning needs through structured Counseling Sessions.

BankBazaar

Senior Customer Relationship Officer jun 2019 - Aug 2020

Responsible for analysing and planning overall customer service excellence, developing and reviewing process review and implementing customer service process review initiatives.

Nexxio

Customer Success Associate jun 2017 - Apr 2019

SAAS platform Success professional focused on ensuring customers effectively utilize a product or service, driving customer satisfaction, retention, and success through excellent service and strategic support.